[{"answer": " Yeah", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Cheever-Letters.txt", "asentId": 3, "question": "I didn't burn it down", "qsentId": 2}, {"answer": " I wonder how my friend's father's going to react to this. Alright, wha", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Cheever-Letters.txt", "asentId": 5, "question": "We could build a cabin like  that", "qsentId": 4}, {"answer": " Well, maybe not us, but two men could", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Cheever-Letters.txt", "asentId": 7, "question": "What, you got a problem with the pen now", "qsentId": 6}, {"answer": "Well, you know, I gotta go to, uh, my friend's parent's house for dinner.. and, you know, I want to shower first.. and I want to leave myself plenty of time", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Cheever-Letters.txt", "asentId": 9, "question": "I think we got a bite on it.   ", "qsentId": 8}, {"answer": "What", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Cheever-Letters.txt", "asentId": 11, "question": "I didn't care much for his jokes", "qsentId": 10}, {"answer": "Well, the thing is.", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Cheever-Letters.txt", "asentId": 13, "question": "Well, the", "qsentId": 12}, {"answer": "I don't know, they're working on a whole other level.", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Cheever-Letters.txt", "asentId": 15, "question": "So we go back to my apartment.", "qsentId": 14}, {"answer": " Alright, alright, hold on!  Time out! Woah, woah!  What did she say", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Cheever-Letters.txt", "asentId": 17, "question": "No, I don't know. How do I know the usual", "qsentId": 16}, {"answer": "Of course", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Cheever-Letters.txt", "asentId": 19, "question": " \"The panties your mother laid out for yo", "qsentId": 18}, {"answer": "Okay? So, she's taking about her panties, so, uh.. So, I said,", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Cheever-Letters.txt", "asentId": 21, "question": " I don't know! It just popped out", "qsentId": 20}, {"answer": "Alright", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Cheever-Letters.txt", "asentId": 23, "question": " I go", "qsentId": 22}, {"answer": "Come in, we're taking a break", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Cheever-Letters.txt", "asentId": 25, "question": "Yeah", "qsentId": 24}, {"answer": "So, my friend, what is this about", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Cheever-Letters.txt", "asentId": 27, "question": " Cigars", "qsentId": 26}, {"answer": " Cigars", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Cheever-Letters.txt", "asentId": 29, "question": " Cigars", "qsentId": 28}, {"answer": " Who's my friend?! Who's my friend?", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Cheever-Letters.txt", "asentId": 31, "question": "I want to know who my friend is", "qsentId": 30}, {"answer": "Uh, heading out. my friend really hates to miss the coming attractions", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Cheever-Letters.txt", "asentId": 33, "question": "yeah, time is what he's indicating there.", "qsentId": 32}, {"answer": "No foolin", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Cheever-Letters.txt", "asentId": 35, "question": " Alright, I got, uh, you come in, you say", "qsentId": 34}, {"answer": "Uh! I made a friend when I was in that place, okay?! And we've been in touch, and my friend told my friend", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Cheever-Letters.txt", "asentId": 37, "question": " \"Anything els", "qsentId": 36}]